Mittenthal, Richard Papers 6407
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Richard Mittenthal Papers
1952-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mittenthal, Richard
6407
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Papers.
9199316
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 03, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 18, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
9199316
- AT and T through Aluminum Company of America, 1974-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AT&T Corporation, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    3/11/2005
    Format: Arbitration Case.
  - Item 2: AT&T Corporation, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    4/8/2005
  - Item 3: Acme Industries, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    7/23/1965
  - Item 4: Action Distributing, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    10/7/1998
  - Item 5: Adams Publishing, Tribune, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    3/15/1989
  - Item 6: Adams Publishing, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    12/16/1991
  - Item 7: Ajax Forging and Casting, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    9/16/1991
  - Item 8: AK Steel Corporation, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    11/10/1997
  - Item 9: AK Steel Corporation, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1/21/1998
  - Item 10: White Industrial Power, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    10/21/1974
  - Item 11: RC Allen Business Machines, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1/8/1962
  - Item 12: Allied Signal, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    7/12/1990
  - Item 13: Allied Supermarkets, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    5/6/1984
  - Item 14: Allied Systems, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    2/17/1998
  - Item 15: Allied Systems, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    2/18/1998
  - Item 16: Alpha Press Machine, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    10/12/1968
  - Item 17: Aluminum Steel Company, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    3/16/1968
  - Item 18: Aluminum Steel Company, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    5/20/1968
- American Cyanamid through Anker-Holth, 1968-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Cyanamid, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    2/24/1975
  - Item 2: American Makes v. Benders, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    12/1/1959
  - Item 3: American Safety Equipment, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    7/29/1967
  - Item 4: American Safety Equipment, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/3/1963
  - Item 5: American Steel Founders, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    10/7/1967
  - Item 6: American Steel Founders, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/3/1969
  - Item 7: American Steel Founders, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    10/1/1969
  - Item 8: American Steel Founders, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11/25/1970
  - Item 9: American Steel Founders, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    12/1/1970
  - Item 10: American Steel Founders, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    7/16/1979
  - Item 11: American Steel Sales, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/12/1969
  - Item 12: American Steulizer Company, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/29/1985
  - Item 13: Ameutick Information Suppliers, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    10/20/1995
  - Item 14: Anaconda American Brass Company, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/7/1971
  - Item 15: Anaconda American Brass Company, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    8/1/1973
  - Item 16: Anaconda American Brass Company, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11/3/1975
  - Item 17: Anaconda American Brass Company, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    12/22/1975
  - Item 18: Anaconda American Brass Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    1/5/1976
  - Item 19: City of Anderson, Industry (Firefighters), 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    9/6/2001
  - Item 20: Wellman Anderson Health Division, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    9/23/1964
- Arizona Public Services through Auto Specialists, 1974-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Arizona Public Services, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/19/1978
  - Item 2: Arizona Public Services, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    9/28/1984
  - Item 3: Arizona Public Services, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/25/1986
  - Item 4: Arizona Public Services, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    10/21/1988
  - Item 5: Arizona Public Services, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    5/22/1974
  - Item 6: Armco Steel Corproration, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    6/16/1975
  - Item 7: Armco Steel Corproration, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/14/1975
  - Item 8: Armco Steel Corproration, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/21/1975
  - Item 9: Armco Steel Corproration, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2/10/1977
  - Item 10: Armco Steel Corproration, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/28/1975
  - Item 11: Armco Steel Corproration, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    5/16/1977
  - Item 12: Armco Steel Corproration, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    6/13/1977
  - Item 13: Aiven Industries, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    3/9/1984
  - Item 14: Arlans Deparment Store, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    10/1/1965
  - Item 15: Armco Steel Corporation, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    4/29/1960
  - Item 16: Armco Steel Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2/19/1974
  - Item 17: Armco Steel Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2/25/1974
  - Item 18: Armco Steel Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    5/4/1974
  - Item 19: Armco Steel Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    3/18/1974
  - Item 20: Armco Steel Corporation, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    3/12/1975
  - Item 21: Armco Steel Corporation, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Auburn Gear, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2/24/2000
  - Item 23: Auto-Alliance International, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    10/21/1993
  - Item 24: Automotive Plastic Technologies, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Auto Specilties Manufacturing, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    12/5/1974
- Babcock and Wilcox through E. W. Bliss, 1969-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Babcock & Wilcox Company, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    12/30/1981
  - Item 2: Babcock & Wilcox Company, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    11/18/1983
  - Item 3: Babcock & Wilcox Company, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    8/2/1985
  - Item 4: Babcock & Wilcox Company, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    7/29/1988
  - Item 5: Bay Oslcopathic Hospital, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    11/1/1976
  - Item 6: Bell Telephone, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    10/2/1978
  - Item 7: Bendix Corporation, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    10/29/1985
  - Item 8: Bendix Corporation, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    6/29/1985
  - Item 9: Allied Corporation, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Allied Signal, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    1/20/1987
  - Item 11: Allied Signal, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    5/11/1987
  - Item 12: Allied Signal, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    7/10/1987
  - Item 13: Allied Signal, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    9/20/1988
  - Item 14: Allied Signal, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Bethlehem Steel, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    5/3/1982
  - Item 16: Blaw-Knox Company, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3/19/1955
  - Item 17: Blaw-Knox Company, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    5/26/1969
  - Item 18: E W Bless Company, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3/13/1984
  - Item 19: E W Bless Company, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3/14/1984
- Bloomfield Hills through Bucyrus-Erie, 1967-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Board of Education Bloomfield, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    5/12/1999
  - Item 2: Bloomfield Township (Fire), 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    5/18/1995
  - Item 3: Blue Care Network - Health Central, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    3/16/1990
  - Item 4: Blue Ridge Paper Products, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    10/1/2002
  - Item 5: Border Company, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    7/17/1972
  - Item 6: Borg -Warner Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    9/18/1979
  - Item 7: Borg -Warner Corporation, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1/3/1983
  - Item 8: Borg -Warner Corporation, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    7/2/1987
  - Item 9: Borg -Warner Corporation, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    9/7/1989
  - Item 10: Rt. Borch Corporation, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    6/15/2000
  - Item 11: Boston Edison, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1/28/1947
  - Item 12: Brass Craft, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    8/28/2001
  - Item 13: Budapest Brass Company, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    2/11/1958
  - Item 14: Buckeye Steel Casting, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    9/20/2000
  - Item 15: Bucyros - Erie Company, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    6/10/1967
  - Item 16: Bucyros - Erie Company, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    6/18/1979
  - Item 17: Bucyros - Erie Company, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    3/1/1979
- Burns International Security through Chris-Craft, 1968-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Burns Intenational Security, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    2/1/1984
  - Item 2: Buschman Company, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5/4/2000
  - Item 3: Cadillac Overall Supply Company, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    9/1/1959
  - Item 4: Cadillac Overall Supply Company, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    4/19/1960
  - Item 5: Caden Plastery Company, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5/30/1962
  - Item 6: Caliemet & Hecla, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    8/27/1963
  - Item 7: Caliemet & Hecla, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Caliemet & Hecla, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    10/1/1967
  - Item 9: Caliemet & Hecla, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    8/13/1968
  - Item 10: Caliemet & Hecla, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5/4/1968
  - Item 11: Canada Dry, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    7/19/1971
  - Item 12: City of Cape Coral (Police), 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    1/6/2000
  - Item 13: Capital Newspaper, Hearst, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    8/1/1970
  - Item 14: Carbon Under, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5/11/1960
  - Item 15: Cargill Incorporated, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    6/4/1982
  - Item 16: Cargill Incorporated, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    8/31/1999
  - Item 17: Carpenter Technology Corporation, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    12/19/1988
  - Item 18: 1 Case Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    3/15/1976
  - Item 19: 1 Case Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: 1 Case Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    6/2/1976
  - Item 21: Cassens Transport Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Cassens Transport Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Cassens Transport Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    3/4/1998
  - Item 24: Cassens Transport Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    4/3/1998
  - Item 25: Caterpillar Corporation, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    1/8/1993
  - Item 26: Central Quality Service Corporation, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    9/10/1993
  - Item 27: Center Line Board of Education, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    12/9/1998
  - Item 28: Central Quality Services, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    10/29/2000
  - Item 29: Cies-Craft Corporation, 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    10/29/1954
- Cleveland Cliffs Iron through Consolidated Paper, 1967-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cleveland Cliffs Iron Corporation, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    7/3/1967
  - Item 2: Cleveland Cliffs Iron Corporation, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    6/15/1970
  - Item 3: Clevenand Electric Illuminating Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    3/19/1979
  - Item 4: Plain Dealer Publishing Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    9/10/1982
  - Item 5: Coca Cola Bottlery of Michigan, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    11/1/1997
  - Item 6: Columbia Broadcasting Systems, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    7/30/1968
  - Item 7: Columbia Gas of Ohio, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    9/3/1981
  - Item 8: Columbus Auto Parts, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    10/9/1964
  - Item 9: Comcast of South Florida, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    9/18/2003
  - Item 10: Commonwealth Edison, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    4/10/1964
  - Item 11: Commonwealth Land J.V., 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    8/26/1982
  - Item 12: Community Health Association, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Container Corporation of America through Cutrale Citrus Juices, 1976-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Containers Corpoation of America, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    2/15/1982
  - Item 2: Containers Corpoation of America, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    7/9/1982
  - Item 3: Continental Airlines, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    7/26/1976
  - Item 4: Continental Airlines, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    4/2/1980
  - Item 5: Conveyor Engineering Company, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    3/6/1978
  - Item 6: Cook Paint & Varnish Company, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    10/15/1973
  - Item 7: Cook Paint & Varnish Company, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    9/14/1979
  - Item 8: Coal Industrial Coatings, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    9/21/1979
  - Item 9: Copper Range Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    6/1/1982
  - Item 10: Copperweld Corporation, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    7/18/1983
  - Item 11: Cox Instrument Corporation, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    11/4/1984
  - Item 12: Corning Incorporated, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    10/20/1998
  - Item 13: Crowley Milner & Company, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    7/5/1977
  - Item 14: Crown Cork & Seal, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    11/24/1997
  - Item 15: Crown Cork & Seal, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    11/29/2000
  - Item 16: Crown Packing, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    4/19/1977
  - Item 17: Cutrale Citrus Juices, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1/19/1999
- Dana Corporation through Detroit Board of Education, 1966-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Dana Corporation, 1905; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    6/22/1905
  - Item 2: Dearborn Inn, Michigan, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/22/1974
  - Item 3: Dearborn Inn, Michigan, Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Dearborn Board of Education, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    5/17/1996
  - Item 5: John Deere, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    11/16/1966
  - Item 6: John Deere, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4/22/1967
  - Item 7: John Deere, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/8/1967
  - Item 8: Delfield Company, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1/21/1997
  - Item 9: Degusse Corpoation (Steel), 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/1/2001
  - Item 10: Delta Dental Plan of Michigan, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/7/1983
  - Item 11: Board of Education - Detroit, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/13/1998
  - Item 12: City of Detroit (Building), 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    12/1/1982
  - Item 13: City of Detroit (Building), 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4/28/1982
  - Item 14: Detroit Board of Education, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    3/14/1997
  - Item 15: Detroit Board of Education, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    8/13/1998
- Detroit Fire Department through Diamond Power Specialty, 1968-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: City of Detroit (Fire Department), 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/12/1973
  - Item 2: Detroit Police Department, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/12/1971
  - Item 3: Detroit Police Department, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    7/10/1972
  - Item 4: Detroit Police Department, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    10/29/1974
  - Item 5: Detroit Police Department, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    8/26/1976
  - Item 6: City of Detroit Public Lighters, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    11/26/1973
  - Item 7: City of Detroit, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    3/5/1976
  - Item 8: Detroit Restauraunt Build (Stouffers), 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/3/1964
  - Item 9: City of Detroit (Supevisors), 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    8/23/2005
  - Item 10: Detroit Steel Corporation, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    8/17/1968
  - Item 11: Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/15/1975
  - Item 12: Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/22/1975
  - Item 13: Detoit Typograpghical Union, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    11/18/1971
  - Item 14: Detroit Unit Exchange Company Metallizing Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    10/14/1963
  - Item 15: Diamond Power Specialty Company, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    7/8/1988
- Dispatch Printing through Dura Corporation, 1966-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Dispatch Printing Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    12/13/1970
  - Item 2: Domestic Lener Supply Company, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    5/18/1992
  - Item 3: Donaldson Company, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    5/28/1981
  - Item 4: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    6/20/1966
  - Item 5: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    9/16/1967
  - Item 6: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    10/14/1967
  - Item 7: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    10/12/1970
  - Item 8: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    10/26/1970
  - Item 9: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    5/12/1971
  - Item 10: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    12/6/1971
  - Item 11: Donner-Hanna Coke Company, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    6/4/1973
  - Item 12: Dow Chemical, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    1/2/1986
  - Item 13: Dow Chemical, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    10/18/2002
  - Item 14: Dow Corning, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    11/28/1972
  - Item 15: Dow Corning, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    12/12/1969
  - Item 16: Dura Corporation, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    10/1/1962
- E and L Transport through Exelon Corporation, 1978-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: E & L Transport Company, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    12/4/1997
  - Item 2: City of East Grand Rapids, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    11/22/1997
  - Item 3: Board of Education School District East Lansing, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    8/6/1993
  - Item 4: Eastern Michigan University, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    5/8/1978
  - Item 5: Eaton County Board of Commissioners Sheriff Department, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    10/4/2002
  - Item 6: Eaton Manufacturing Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    7/13/1964
  - Item 7: Edison Sanlt Elective, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    12/1/1981
  - Item 8: Electric Auto-Lite Company, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    3/9/1959
  - Item 9: Electric Auto-Lite Company, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    8/16/1960
  - Item 10: Electric Auto-Lite Company, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    9/1/1966
  - Item 11: Electric Auto-Lite Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    9/14/1964
  - Item 12: ESB Incorporated, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    3/31/1980
  - Item 13: Everfresh Incorporated, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    8/13/1993
  - Item 14: Even nude Motors Octboad Marine Corporation, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Even nude Motors Octboad Marine Corporation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    3/30/1982
  - Item 16: Ex-Cell-O Corporation, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    12/18/1961
  - Item 17: Ex-Cell-O Corporation, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    7/17/1963
  - Item 18: Exelon Corporation, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    9/25/2003
- Fairchild Republic through Frito-Lay, 1969-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Fairchild Republic, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    10/7/1983
  - Item 2: Federal Creosoting Company, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    5/14/1957
  - Item 3: Federal Mogul Bower Bearings, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    1/1/1961
  - Item 4: Federal Mogul Bower Bearings, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    5/29/1964
  - Item 5: Federal Screw Workers, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    3/28/2001
  - Item 6: Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    10/7/1978
  - Item 7: Fenestra Incorporated, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    2/22/1958
  - Item 8: Davidson Enamel Products - Fenestra, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    11/11/1955
  - Item 9: Flechtner Brothers, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    8/10/1982
  - Item 10: City of Flint, Michigan Board of Education, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    4/22/1996
  - Item 11: FMC Corporation - John Bean Division, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    3/22/1966
  - Item 12: FMC Corporation - John Bean Division, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    3/20/1978
  - Item 13: Ford, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    11/30/1965
  - Item 14: Ford, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    3/25/1968
  - Item 15: Ford, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    12/26/1969
  - Item 16: Ford, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    9/19/1976
  - Item 17: Ford, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    9/27/1976
  - Item 18: Ford, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    3/16/1982
  - Item 19: Ford, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    5/11/1968
  - Item 20: Ford, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    2/3/1995